University of Connecticut, Office of Public Information (OPI) Records 1979.0011
Archives & Special Collections at the Thomas J. Dodd Research Center, University of Connecticut Libraries
- Series II: Office Files, undated, 1918-1980
  - 1961-1978 (Box 7)
    - Minority and Women Enrollment and Staff (Minority Enrollment), 1973-1975
    - Mission of the University, 1975-1976
    - Mobil Vending Unit Fees, 1976
    - Moratorium, 1969
    - Museum of Art, 1974-1975
    - Music Department, 1974-1975
    - Narcotics, etc. on campus, 1966-1971
    - National Science Foundation, 196219-66
    - Neural Sciences Group, 1968-1969
    - New England Center for Continuing Education (Durham Declaration), 1967-1974
    - New England Magazine, Leon H. Ballou, Jr., 1966
    - New England Weekly Press Association, 1964
    - New Hampshire, University of, 1968-1976
    - New clippings-miscellaneous, 1956-1963, 1977; (2 folders)
    - News Releases, 1961-1964
    - News Releases, other colleges, 1964-69
    - Newsletter, U of C mailing list, 1963, 1977
    - Newsletter correspondence, 1964-1965
    - Newsletter from other colleges, 1963-1974
    - Newspapers, 1961-1977
    - Newspapers, out of state, 1962
    - Noble, Dan, 1968
    - North End Hartford-Inner City Projects, 1967-1969
    - OPI - Commitment, 1968-1975
    - Outreach, 1978
    - OWLS - Order of Women Legislators, 1967
    - Pharmacy, School of, 1965-1975
    - Physical Plant (Landscape Dept.), 1974-1976
    - Plant Maintenance Dept., 1962-1970
    - Post Office, U. S. - Storrs, 1967-1974
    - Radio-TV Center, 1968-1969 (Box 11)
    - Rutgers News Service, 1963-1969
    - Saturday School, 1971-1972
    - School of Business Administration
      - Faculty, 1968-1978
      - General, 1972-1980; (3 folders)
      - Students, 1968-1975
    - Science Writers Tour, 1967-1968
    - Sea-Grant Universities, 1965-1966
    - Search Committee (President), 1978
    - Security Side arms Issue, 1968-1969
    - Shea, Gail A., Asst. Provost, 1971-1973
    - Sigma Delta Chi, 1961-1973
    - Skating Rink, 1967
    - E. O. Smith High School Grievance Policy, 1975
    - E. O. Smith High School Flap, 1976
    - Speakers (visiting) Policy, 1975
    - Speeches, 1960-1965
    - Spengemann, William C., 1966
    - Sports Information, 1975-1977
    - Storrs Shopping Complex, 1968-1972
    - Stratton, John, 1971-1973
    - Student Leaves, 1971
    - Student Union Board of Governors, Minutes, 1977
    - Students-Rights-Power, 1968 (Box 12)
    - Students-Selective Service, 1966-1971
    - Surveys, 1964
    - Tax Credit for College Students, 1967
    - Russell I. Thackrey Collection - Wilbur Cross Library, 1969
    - Theater, Department of. Cecil Hinkel, 1965-1969
    - Tiernan Case, 1970-1971
    - Time Magazine, 1966
    - Transportation Institute, 1974, 1978
    - (De)Tripling [Housing], 1974-1975
    - Tuition (Student), 1971
    - Tuition (Clippings), 1971
    - UCONN Bookstore, 1973-1975
    - UCONN Budget, 1974-1976; (2 folders)
    - UCONN Building Progress, 1969, 1976
    - UCONN Chronicle, David Kimball, Editor, 1971-1975
    - UCONN Newspaper, 1969-1975
    - UCONN Quality, 1967
    - United Educators, 1966
    - University Extension Forum, 1967
    - University Extension Study Committee, 1966
    - University Press, 1965
    - Vermont, University of, 1972-1975
    - Von der Mehden>, 1968-1974
    - Waterbury higher Education Complex, 1971
    - Waturbury Marine Recruiting, undated
    - Waugh, Albert E., 1961-1964
    - Weber, C. A., 1962
    - Whalen, Michael, 1970
    - Wilson, Kenneth G., Vice President, Academic Affairs, 1974-1976
    - Women-Classified, 1974
    - Woodrow Wilson Fellowship Foundation, 1965
    - Yale University, G. Clinton Jones, IV, Director Of Sports Information, 1963-1972
- Series III: Office of Sports Information, undated, 1921-1981
  - Athletic Communications Office Records.
- Series IV: Scrapbooks, 1921-1983
  - Connecticut Agricultural College (Volume 1)
    - 1921-1935
  - Connecticut State College
    - 1936-1937 (Volume 2)
    - 1937-1938 (Volume 3)
  - University of Connecticut
    - 1939-1940 (Volume 4)
    - 1940-1941 (Volume 5)
    - 1943-1946 (Volume 6)
    - 1953-1961 (Volume 7)
    - 1960-1964 (Volume 8)
    - 1961-1964 (Volume 9)
    - 1964-1966 (Volume 10)
    - 1965 (Volume 11)
    - 1966-1969 (Volume 12)
    - 1969-1970 (Volume 13)
    - 1970-1971 (Volume 14)
    - 1972 (Volume 15)
    - 1972-1974 (Volume 16)
    - 1975-1976 (Volume 17)
    - 1976-1978 (Volume 18)
    - 1979-1980 (Volume 19)
    - 1980-1982 (Volume 20)
    - 1982-1983 (Volume 21)
- Series V: News Releases, 1954-1989
  - News Release Listings
    - 1961-1977 (Volume A)
    - 1977-1983, 1989: April - July (Volume B)
  - News Releases
    - 1954 December - 1957 May (Othertype 1)
    - 1957 May - 1959 March (Othertype 2)
    - 1959 March - 1960 May (Othertype 3)
    - 1960 July - 1961 February (Othertype 4)
    - 1961 March - December (Othertype 5)
    - 1962 January - September (Othertype 6)
    - 1962 September 1963 July (Othertype 7)
    - 1963 July - 1964 April (Othertype 8)
    - 1964 May - 1965 March (Othertype 9)
    - 1965 March - November (Othertype 10)
    - 1965 November - 1966 July (Othertype 11)
    - 1966 July - 1967 March (Othertype 12)
    - 1967 March - 1971 December (Othertype 13)
    - 1972 - 1973 (Othertype 14)
    - 1974 (Othertype 15)
    - 1975 (Othertype 16)
    - 1976 (Othertype 17)
    - 1977 (Othertype 18)
    - 1978 January - June (Othertype 19)
    - 1978 July - December (Othertype 20)
    - 1979 January - June (Othertype 21)
    - 1979 July - December (Othertype 22)
    - 1980 January - June (Othertype 23)
    - 1980 July - December (Othertype 24)
    - 1981 January - June (Othertype 25)
    - 1981 July - December (Othertype 26)
    - 1982 January - June (Othertype 27)
    - 1982 July - December (Othertype 28)
    - 1983 January - June (Othertype 29)
    - 1983 July - December (Othertype 30)
    - 1984 January - June (Othertype 31)
    - 1984 July - December (Othertype 32)
    - 1985 January - June (Othertype 33)
    - 1985 July - December (Othertype 34)
    - 1986 October - December (Othertype 35)
    - 1987 January - April
    - 1982 January - June (Othertype 36)
    - 1982 July - December (Othertype 37)
    - 1983 January - May (Othertype 38)
    - 1983 June - December (Othertype 39)
    - 1984 January - June (Othertype 40)
    - 1984 July - December (Othertype 41)
    - 1985 January - May (Othertype 42)
    - 1985 June - December (Othertype 43)
    - 1986 (Othertype 44)
    - 1987 January - 1988 March (Othertype 45)
    - 1988 April (Othertype 46)
- Series VI: Biographical Files, 1957-1978
  - Abramson, Stephen (Box 1)
  - Abromson, Morton
  - Adams, John
  - Addona, Antoinette
  - Adelsperger, Walter
  - Adotte, George
  - Ahlberg, Evelyn
  - Agarmala, Vinod
  - Ahmad, Imtiaz
  - Aitken, Janet
  - Akeroyd, Joanne
  - Akerstein, Louise
  - Alanen, Jack D.
  - Alba, Immaculata
  - Albert, Robert
  - Albertson, Vaughn
  - Alibion, Robert
  - Alexander, Robert
  - Alexander, S.
  - Allabnek, Steven
  - Allen, John
  - Allen, Shirley
  - Allie, John David
  - Alpers, Robert
  - Altmeyer, Tom
  - Amayo, Dr. Ralph
  - Amdur, Millard J.
  - Amendola, Bonaventure
  - Ammons, Elizabeth
  - Ammons, Mark
  - Amundsen, Lawrence
  - Anaghostakis, Christopher
  - Anderson, Clara
  - Anderson, Jackie Wlater
  - Anderson, Ronald J.
  - Andrews, Daniel K.
  - Andrews, Max
  - Appel, Hansgunter
  - Apperson, Ronald
  - Archibald, Thomas L.
  - Arms, Frank
  - Armentana, Dominic
  - Armstrong, Marguerite
  - Arnold, William
  - Arrington, Dale
  - Ash, Dr. Christopher
  - Asherman, George
  - Aschlock, Peter D.
  - Asmundsson, Mrs. Rijor
  - Asselini, Claire
  - Atallah, Sana
  - Ater, Daniel
  - Atkyns, Robert
  - Audette, Louis
  - Augsburger, Jerry
  - Austin, Joseph
  - Averill, Donald
  - Axelrod, Saul
  - Axman, Donald
  - Bacchus, Wilfred
  - Baccus, R. Gileen
  - Backlund, Arley
  - Bacon, Marilyn
  - Baginski, Leonard
  - Bahnson, Claus
  - Bailey, Brian
  - Baird, Archibald
  - Baker, Dr. Irving
  - Baker, Col. Warren
  - Baldauf, Richard
  - Baldwin, Dewitt
  - Baley, James
  - Ball, L. Andrew
  - Banning, Kent
  - Banning, Jerald
  - Barakant, Fred
  - Barry, Philip
  - Barry, Herbert III
  - Barston, Allen
  - Bartholomew, Edward Jr.
  - Barton, Bruce
  - Baskin, Abraham
  - Bates, Theodore
  - Batti, John
  - Baumon-Neumayer, Tatjana
  - Baumsten, Ida
  - Beam, Burton
  - Beatini, Marie
  - Becker, Dr. Robert
  - Behan, David
  - Bell, Earl
  - Beltran, Mary Jane
  - Benjamin, Jeanne
  - Benson, Maj. Donald
  - Bentley, Bruce
  - Benton, Eileen
  - Bernard, Bruce
  - Bernardi, Vincent
  - Bernstein, Emil
  - Berry, Edward
  - Berthovax, Paul
  - Beshle, Richard
  - Battacharya, Samir Kumar
  - Bibbee, Dr. Richard
  - Bidwell, Gloria
  - Biederman, Ronald
  - Bieszad, Jean
  - Bissell, Linda
  - Blackwell, Henry
  - Blanchard, James
  - Blankenburg, Richard Moore
  - Blechner, Dr. Jack
  - Bliss, Donald
  - Blocker, Robert
  - Boak, Florence
  - Bobb, Arthur
  - Bobrove, Arthur
  - Boelke, Jane
  - Boettingen, Edward
  - Bogan, Larry
  - Boggard, Ronald
  - Bok, William
  - Boland, John
  - Boland Walter
  - Boota, Marcella Spann
  - Borrero, Michael
  - Bosmajian, Haig
  - Bosworth, Karl
  - Bowden, Francine
  - Bozzuto, James
  - Bramblett, Jerry
  - Brandon, Capt. Eddie
  - Braun, Molly F.
  - Bray, June
  - Breen, Joseph
  - Breen, Lee Holcolmbe
  - Breetz, William Jr.
  - Breinich, John
  - Brennan, James
  - Breslow, Richard
  - Bretti, Richard
  - Brick, James
  - Brinnin, John
  - Brissman, Lily
  - Brndhurst, Allan
  - Brock, C. Raymond
  - Broden, Barry
  - Brodtkorb, Paul Jr.
  - Brotman, Michael
  - Brown, Catherine Havens
  - Brown, David Lile
  - Brown, Doris
  - Brown, Gary
  - Brown, Mrs. Helen G.
  - Brown, Henry
  - Brown, Patrick
  - Brown, William
  - Bronnell, James
  - Bronnell, Sam
  - Brubaker, Mary Susan
  - Bruch, Frank
  - Brumbach, Joseph
  - Brunell, Louise
  - Buddington, Barbara
  - Buggaef, Alexis
  - Bunt, George
  - Burke, Brian
  - Buss, James
  - Burke, Harold
  - Burnight, Robert
  - Butler, Ernest
  - Butterfield, William
  - Byrnes, Capt. Vincent. Jr.
  - Cagnon, Maurice (Box 2)
  - Callender, Marie
  - Calvert, Anne Stuart
  - Camp, Leon Raymond
  - Camp, W. H.
  - Campbell, George Stuart
  - Cancro, Robert
  - Capron, Elizabeth
  - Cardner, Mary Ellen
  - Carey, Roberta A.
  - Carloni, Luigi
  - Carlsen, James
  - Carlson, Julie
  - Carney, Larry
  - Carpentieri, Ida
  - Carr, Karen
  - Carroll, Murray
  - Casey, Murray Joseph
  - Casler, Lt. Frederick
  - Castaldi, Cosmo
  - Caster, Robert
  - Caswell, Hal
  - Cattanach, David
  - Ceccarelli, Romolo
  - Chadbourne, Juan
  - Chambers, Helen
  - Chameides, Leon
  - Chandler, John
  - Chandler, Margaret
  - Chandler, Warren
  - Chang, Charity
  - Chapin, Frank
  - Chapple, Wendy
  - Chase, Howard
  - Chen, Hsing-Yao
  - Cheney, William Fitch
  - Chiburis, Edward F.
  - Chimini, Leroy
  - Chimietenski, Gail
  - Choate, Jerry
  - Choduhury, Leo
  - Churchill, Thomas
  - Cibrochi, Georgette
  - Ciola, Dr. Benjamin
  - Clack, Mrs. Alice
  - Clair, Capt. Carl
  - Clark, Borbala
  - Clark, Hector
  - Clark, Theresa
  - Clark, William C.
  - Clark, William R.
  - Clay, Vidal
  - Clayborne, David
  - Clayton, Manfred
  - Close, Dr. Darwin
  - Clough, L. Bradley
  - Coachman, Winfield
  - Cobb, William
  - Cobb, Dorothy
  - Coe, Charlotte
  - Cohen, Arnon
  - Cohen, Cheryl
  - Cohen, Dr. Floyd
  - Colburn, Susan
  - Colby, Clarence, Jr.
  - Cole, P.D.H.
  - Coleman, Nancy
  - Collier, Alan Graham
  - Collier, Mary
  - Collins, Dr. Duane R.
  - Collins, John
  - Colton, Dr. Ethan T. III
  - Comella, Vincent
  - Condron, Edward
  - Coniam, Charles
  - Contessa, Barbara
  - Conzemius, Rosemary
  - Cooker, Harry S.
  - Coon, Geraldine
  - Cooper, Anthony
  - Miss Coppino
  - Corbett, Roger
  - Corcoran, A Wayne
  - Corcoran, Gerald
  - Corliss, John
  - Corliss, William
  - Cornell, Donald
  - Cornish, Roger
  - Corrigan, Marjorie
  - Corson, Peter
  - Corwin, Arthur
  - Cosenza, Benjamin
  - Costas, John
  - Costanini, Arthur
  - Cotter, Paul
  - Courter, Monte
  - Covey, Irene
  - Cowan, Thaddeus
  - Craddock, Roy
  - Crain, Alan
  - Crane, Carlson
  - Crawford, Charles
  - Crane, Carl
  - Cronin, Daniel
  - Crompton, Richard
  - Cross, Dr. Herbert
  - Crossman, Bradford
  - Crowne, Douglas
  - Cruse, Victor
  - Cummings, Robert
  - Cummings, Robert J.
  - Cummings, Thomas
  - Cuperman, Pedro
  - Curl, David
  - Curle, Harold
  - Cushman, Bigelow
  - Curry, Thomas F.
  - Curtis, Dr. Lawrence
  - Cutts, Norm
  - Daley, James S.
  - Dalton, Clare
  - Damjanor, Ivan
  - Dammers, Robin
  - Dan, Robert
  - Dane, Jeffrey
  - Danforth, Susan
  - Darrow, Diane
  - Darwin, Roy Jr.
  - Davids, Resa
  - Davidson, Thomas
  - Davidson, William
  - Davis, Carole
  - Davis, Katherine
  - Davis, Wendell
  - Dawson, Robert
  - Dean, David
  - Decker, Frederick
  - DeCorrevont, Col. Leon
  - Decoursey, Russell
  - Defulrio, Eugine
  - Dehenes, Richard
  - Deininger, Robert
  - Dekay, Col. Richard
  - Delegre, Alain
  - Deluca, Virginia
  - Dents, Robert
  - Dennis, Joseph Jr.
  - Desrosiers, Richard
  - Dest, Harry Jr.
  - Deutsch, Joel
  - Devre, Robert
  - Deupree, Annie Jo
  - Deveraux, Capt. R. A.
  - Dewey, Arthur
  - DiCecco, Mrs. Marie G. Jr.
  - Dicenzo, Robert
  - Dickerson, Ronald
  - Dickie, Peggy Ann
  - Dickson, John
  - Didier, Maureen C.
  - DiFilippo, Francine
  - Dimler, Thomas
  - Dinegar, Caroline
  - Diner, Alexander
  - Dinsmore, Jean
  - Dirlam, Juel
  - DiRocco, Pat
  - Dixon, James K.
  - Dizikes, John
  - Doane, Raymond
  - Dodd, Martina
  - Dodge, Homer
  - Doherty, Michael
  - Dolyak, Frank
  - Donadello, Gloria
  - Donahue, Raymond
  - Donovan, Peter
  - Dorbin, Sanford
  - Dorbuck, Anthony (Box 3)
  - Dougherty, William
  - Dowd, Leonard
  - Doyle, Dr. F.L.
  - Doyle, Grace
  - Doyle, Warner
  - Duncan, Roy
  - Dragat, John
  - Drake, Thelbert
  - Drehen, John
  - Driscoll, Paul
  - Duffy, John
  - Dugas, James
  - Dunlop, John P. Jr.
  - Dunn, John M.
  - Dye, Ella
  - Dye, Scott
  - Early, Edward
  - Ebbin, Mrs. Marilyn
  - Eblen, Jack
  - Eckerlin, Ralph
  - Edens, Dr. David
  - Edwards, Melvin
  - Ehrenpreis, Charles
  - Eisenbach, Rabbi Shalom
  - Elliot, Ethel Mary
  - Elliot, Orville
  - Ellison, Gaythe Sodoski
  - Ellsworth, Dianne
  - Ellsworth, James Dennis
  - Emmel, Hildegard
  - Endrich, Frederick
  - Engelhardt, Dean Lee
  - Ephrath, Aryl
  - Epstein, Donald
  - Epstein, Rhoda
  - Ergin, Florence
  - Ericson, Jon
  - Estes, James
  - Erarts, Barbara
  - Eukers, Mary
  - Evans, John
  - Everett, Miriam
  - Ezban, Selim
  - Fabrikant, Jacob
  - Fagan, Aligia
  - Fahm, Lottie
  - Fairweather, Robert
  - Faksh, Mahmud
  - Fallows, Marjorie
  - Farling, Myrtlegene
  - Farnsworth, Bill
  - Faulkner, Sylvia
  - Fawcett, Jacqueline
  - Fedorczyk, Viola
  - Feeney, Marian
  - Feldman, Chester
  - Feldstone, Charles
  - Felsenfeld, Herbert
  - Fenstermacher, Helen
  - Ferguson, Charles
  - Fernandez, Pelayo
  - Ferrar, Carl
  - Ferrill, Mitchell
  - Fersh, George
  - Feverman, Zolton
  - Fields, David
  - Findlay, Merlin III
  - Finlay, Bill
  - Fiondella, Mario
  - Fischer, Carl
  - Fischer, Mary
  - Fischer, David
  - Fischer, Jean
  - Fischer, William
  - Fishman, David
  - Fitch, Robert
  - Fitzpatrick, James
  - Flanagan, Douglas Jr.
  - Fleming, David
  - Fletcher, Charles
  - Focht, Thodore
  - Fonda, Charles
  - Foote, Roberta
  - Fontaine, Patrick Jr.
  - Forbis, Roger
  - Ford, Joe Taylor
  - Foresti, Roy Jr.
  - Forscher, Louise
  - Forslund, Morris
  - Forst, Arthur
  - Forte, Elsie
  - Forzano, Richard
  - Foster, John
  - Fowler, Irving
  - Fox, Douglas
  - France, George
  - France, Ruth
  - Frank, Roland
  - Franks, Francis
  - Franz, David
  - Frazier, Monte
  - French, Mildred
  - Freidmann, Dr. Felix
  - Fridshal, Donald
  - Friedler, Betty
  - Friedmean, Norman
  - Friedman, Gilbert
  - Froning, Glenn
  - Fulcher, Audrey
  - Fuller, James
  - Furshpan, Anita
  - Galloway, James
  - Gadbois, Stuart
  - Gaffney, John
  - Gall, Marshall
  - Galetti, Pierre
  - Galvin, Robert
  - Ganotz, Theodore
  - Garfunkel, Frank
  - Garber, Herbert
  - Garrigue, Jean
  - Garvine, Richard
  - Gatling, Wade
  - Gaunya, William
  - Gauvin, Jane
  - Geach, Barbara
  - Gebhardt, Fred
  - Gebner, Martin
  - Genser, Patricia
  - Geoghan, Robert
  - Gebris, Joseph
  - George, Frances
  - Gerhard, George
  - Gersherberg, Irving
  - Getz, Lowell
  - Gilikin, James
  - Gilman, Ralph
  - Gimpel, Bronislaw
  - Girard, Arthur
  - Glove, Helen
  - Griffen, Robert
  - Gladstone, Herbert
  - Glass, Manuel
  - Glazier, Lynn
  - Gleason, John
  - Godar, Thomas
  - Gold, Robert
  - Goldberg, Arthur
  - Goldblatt, Peter
  - Goldman, Bruce
  - Gonczaow, Ladislas
  - Gooch, Brison
  - Goode, R. W.
  - Goodman, Earl Jr.
  - Goodman, John
  - Gostein, Henry
  - Goodwillie, Richard
  - Gordon, Harold
  - Gordon, Michael
  - Gordon, Michael W.
  - Goss, Jean
  - Goss, William
  - Gusslee, David
  - Gottlieb, Roger
  - Govoni, Laura
  - Grandon, John
  - Grasso, John
  - Gratzer, Miklos
  - Gray, John
  - Gerbel, Martin
  - Greef, Albert
  - Green, Joyce
  - Greene, Kenneth
  - Greenspan, Marshall
  - Greenwood, Mary
  - Greer, Hugh
  - Greiner, Donald
  - Gresozyk, Edwin
  - Griffen, Harold
  - Grinnell, Jacque
  - Grisebach, Hans
  - Grissmer, John
  - Griswold, Wilber
  - Gromho, Gerald
  - Gritter, Roy
  - Gris, Elliott
  - Grossfen, Ralph
  - Groth, Joyce
  - Groff, William
  - Gruses, Theodore
  - Guillor, Jean
  - Guiney, Himey M.
  - Gunther-Stein, Dagmar
  - Gunzer, Richard
  - Gurshi, Barbara
  - Gushep, Mary
  - Guftanson, Reuben
  - Haleron, Harold (Box 4)
  - Haber, Michael
  - Hadley, Jerry
  - Hadley, Robert
  - Halbasch, Keith
  - Halp, Harold
  - Hal, Margaret
  - Hall, James
  - Halloran, Thomas
  - Halmes, Terry
  - Hamel, Mary
  - Hamilton, Milton
  - Hamilton, William
  - Hancock, Jim
  - Hand, Frederick
  - Haskins, Olan
  - Hansborough, Louis
  - Hansell, Roger
  - Hansman, Eugene
  - Haraden, Paul
  - Harasymi, Shu
  - Harbaugh, Joseph
  - Harbarge, William
  - Harder, Peter
  - Harlestoa, Jerome
  - Harmon, Leon
  - Harms, Larry
  - Harndom, George
  - Harper, Walter
  - Harrell, Bill
  - Harrington, James
  - Harrington, Robert
  - Harris, Donald
  - Harris, Robert
  - Harrison, Robert
  - Harshberger, Richard
  - Hart, Alan
  - Harth, Dorothea
  - Hartman, Betty
  - Hartman, Stephan
  - Harvey, David
  - Harwell, Joseph
  - Hastings, Frank
  - Hetch, Geoffrey
  - Hauser, Fred
  - Hawker, John
  - Hawkins, Arthur
  - Hawthorne, Ruth
  - Hayes, Evelyn
  - Hazen, Stanley
  - Hejna, Robert
  - Heald, Judith
  - Heath, Brian
  - Hedberg, David
  - Hegrad, Flemming
  - Hegenberger, William
  - Hefner, Charles
  - Hegner, Brenda
  - Hellman, Arthur
  - Helmboldt, Charles
  - Helmboldt, Marie
  - Hendrich, Georgina
  - Hennen, Urbane
  - Herman, James
  - Herrman, Arthur
  - Hermann, Virginia
  - Hesperheide, Henry
  - Hess, Jon
  - Heyd, Allen
  - Hibbard, Bernice
  - Higginbotham, Ronald
  - Hilberg, John
  - Hill, John
  - Hill, Bob
  - Hiner, Leo
  - Hinhel, Martha
  - Hintz, Ray
  - Hinman, Lynn
  - Hirsh, Judith
  - Hirshbard, Marilyn
  - Hollman, Elward
  - Hitt, Sam
  - Houghton, Raymond
  - Hobard, Jean
  - Hochbeiser, Louis
  - Hochman, Larry
  - Hodnett, Frank
  - Hoffman, Dorothy
  - Hoffman, Edith
  - Hogan, Marjory
  - Hogan, Peter
  - Hohnadel, David
  - Holcombe, Lee
  - Holeceb, John
  - Holman, Harold
  - Holsinger, James
  - Holzer, Thomas
  - Holzman, Robert
  - Hopkins, Thomas
  - Horpor, Harold
  - Howard, Franklin
  - Howard, Louis
  - Hoyer, John
  - Hughes, Charles
  - Huizinga, Harry
  - Huhill, Peter
  - Hulse, Judith
  - Hultin, Jill
  - Hunt Allan
  - Hunt, Martin
  - Humphrey, George
  - Humphrey, Eugene
  - Humphrey, Winnifred
  - Hunt, Sara
  - Hunter, Russell
  - Hunter, Margaret
  - Hunter, Ruth
  - Hutchinson, Richard
  - Hyder, Kate
  - Ierardo, Domenick
  - Ilmet, Ivor
  - Infante, Mary Sue
  - Ingman, Stan
  - Inman, Marjorie
  - Irish, Wilmot W.
  - Irvine, Lynn Jr.
  - Irving, Brian
  - Ives, John
  - Ivry, Barbara
  - Izzo, Donato Maria
  - Jackson, Joseph
  - Jackson, Melvin
  - Jacobs, Martin
  - Jacobs, Susan
  - Jacobson, David
  - Jaffe, Marten
  - Jalai, Mehrdad
  - James, Susan
  - James, Byron
  - Jannke, Paul
  - Jarmoc, Edwin
  - Jenkins, G. Franklin
  - Jennings, Walter
  - Jensen, Robert
  - Jewart, Russell
  - Jodaitis, Peter
  - Johnson, Claude
  - Johnson, Henry
  - Johnson, James
  - Johnson, Jean Ellen
  - Johnson, Louise
  - Jolie, Norman
  - Johnston, James Richard
  - Jones, Ellen S.
  - Jones, J. S. Peter
  - Jones, Robert S.
  - Jones, Rodney R.
  - Jones, Thomas Evan
  - Jordan, Ann
  - Jordan, Dr. Gary
  - Jordan, Neal
  - Jordan, Ronald Joseph
  - Jordon, Vera
  - Jorgens, jack
  - Katz, Alfred
  - Kaehrle, William
  - Kahn, Lynda
  - Kahn, Michael
  - Kaiser, Julian
  - Kammer, Harold
  - Kanter, Harry
  - Kaplan, Frank
  - Kapuler, Alan Mitchell
  - Kaseman, Charlotte
  - Kasperson, Roger
  - Katz, Alfred
  - Kaufman, Violet
  - Kays, John
  - Keefe, Josephine
  - Klein, Seymour
  - Keith, Jean
  - Kelley, Francis
  - Keller, Frank
  - Kellog, Seth
  - Kelley, William
  - Kelsey, Seth
  - Kempel, Leo
  - Kendall, John
  - Kendrick, John
  - Kennedy, Mary Jane
  - Kent, Donald
  - Kenyon, Alan
  - Keough, Frank
  - Kevan, Patricia
  - Kiley, Robert
  - Kidder, Marilyn
  - Kidder, Harold
  - Killiam, Lewis
  - Killory, J.F.
  - Kim, Sang-Nam
  - King, Allan
  - King, Timothy
  - Kinney, Jo Ann Smith (Box 5)
  - Kinsman, Dave
  - Kise, Leonard
  - Kistler, J.W.
  - Klee, Bruce
  - Klein, Norman
  - Klepas, Richard Lee
  - Kiett, Donald
  - Klinck, Ross
  - Kline, Ernest
  - Kline, Rufus
  - Klebanan, Diane
  - Klinman, Cynthia
  - Kneisel, John
  - Knepper, Alvin
  - Knightly, Helene
  - Knutson, Thomas
  - Kochenburger, Ralph
  - Koerner, Beverly
  - Kohl, Ruth
  - Koha, Hahs
  - Kolakonski, Donald
  - Koller, John
  - Kopf, Martin
  - Kopp, Thomas
  - Korn, Paul
  - Kornfeld, Joseph
  - Kottman, Barbara Ann
  - Kourias, Eustratioos
  - Kowalczeuski, Audrzej
  - Kozlozeuski, Audrzej
  - Kozlowski, Gene Jr.
  - Kramer, Harold
  - Kranski, Patricia
  - Krilov, Arthur
  - Kritzman, George
  - Kroch, Anthony
  - Kroon, Catherine
  - Kuck, Julius
  - Kuhns, Patricia
  - Kuskih, Anton
  - Kuypers, Henricus
  - Labovitz, Jeffrey Niles
  - LaDuke, Jeanne
  - Laflin, Jack
  - Lafferty, Eugene
  - La Gambina, Joseph
  - Lahey, Henry
  - Lache, Sheldon
  - Lally, Elizabeth
  - Lamb, Jack
  - Lamson, George
  - Landry, Eleanore
  - Langler, Kenneth
  - Lapan, Maureen Dr
  - Laplante, Joseph
  - Larson, Eric
  - Lash, Warren
  - Lattok, Agnes
  - Lau, Thomas, Dr.
  - Lauber, Capt. Robert
  - Lauder, Jean
  - Lauder, William Jr.
  - Laudieri, Mario
  - Lawler, Carroll
  - Leacock, Seth
  - Leaden, Robert
  - Leary, James
  - Leary, Paul
  - Lee, Charles
  - Lee, Tu-Lee
  - Leese, Jason
  - Legg, Bonnie
  - Leggett, Dr. John
  - Lehan, David
  - Lehnert, Oswald
  - Leighton, Helene
  - Leland, Capt. David
  - Leonard, Edward
  - Leston, Dennis
  - Levcowich, Tatiana
  - Levenson, Rosaline
  - Levenstein, Charles
  - Levi, David Michael
  - Levin, Edward
  - Levine, Howard
  - Levit, Donald
  - Leonard, Donald
  - Lerner, Irving
  - Lerner, Max
  - LeRoy, John B.
  - Levit, Donald
  - Devy, Burton
  - Levy, Claude
  - Lewandowski, F. H.
  - Lewis, Phyllis
  - Lewis, Robert
  - Lewis, Theodore Jr.
  - Leyser, Frederic
  - Li, Shu Tung
  - Lien, Charles
  - Lietre, John
  - Light, Robert
  - Lillie, Capt. Marvin
  - Lindgren, Allen
  - Lindley, James
  - Linke, Eugene
  - Lippincott, Barbara
  - Liss, Alan
  - Listro, John
  - Little, Dr. Virginia
  - Littlefield, Neil
  - Lockett, Jerry
  - Lockwood, Patton
  - Loeser, Charles